go4hosting.in 2019-03-22

# Privacy Policy : Go4Hosting

It would behoove you to familiarize yourself with our Privacy Policy, and contact us at Cyfuture India Pvt. Ltd., 197/198, NSEZ, Noida, India - 201301, for any further clarifications.

### PERSONAL INFORMATION: COLLECTION & USAGE

For the purposes of this privacy policy, any information that can potentially identify a person comes under the ambit of “Personal Information”. Cyfuture services request you to provide personal Information when you interact with them, and the information you provide is used in accordance with the Cyfuture Privacy Policy. This information may be used in combination with generic information for various purposes such as marketing & advertising or product development. In case you refrain from providing your personal information, you may not be able to utilize optimum benefits from Cyfuture products.

You might provide your name, email, physical address, phone number, IP address, credit card information among other personal information when you explore our services, take part in a survey, or contact us. Cyfuture collects this data for better recommending suitable products and services.

With your consent, the data you provide is used in accordance with this Privacy Policy, legislative requirements (including region-specific restrictions and guidelines, if any), and legitimate disclosure laws. We use the data we collect to update you about our offerings, feature additions or enhancements, and other updates in relation to the performance & security of our services.

This data is used in the development of new products & services, network & transaction security and financial verification wherever necessary.

Personal information that you provide lets us keep you informed about changes in our products, services, the terms & conditions relating to them, and important security updates. We may use the data for system performance analysis, internal auditing and process improvement purposes. The carrying out of promotional activities and limited-period offers makes use of this data as well. For preventing fraud and illegal financial transactions, we may validate your personal information through comparison with public resources and databases to avoid monetary or privacy loss. 

Third parties also create databases of personal information, which may be acquired and used by us in the development and deployment of our products & services according to prevalent laws governing the usage of such databases. 

### PERSONAL INFORMATION: PROTECTION

Cyfuture is committed to protect your personal information stored with us. We use a variety of security technologies and procedures to help protect your personal data from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. 

### CONSEQUENCES OF NOT PROVIDING PERSONAL INFORMATION

If you choose not to provide your Personal Information when the same is mandatory to process your request, we may not be able to provide the requested service.

### ACCESS, CORRECTION AND OBJECTION OF PERSONAL INFORMATION

Your active participation in keeping the data Cyfuture stores about you is encouraged. You can request us to update your personal information in case of changes or errors, and also request deletion, provided we are not required to retain the data for specified amounts of time by law.

### SHARING WITH OR DISCLOSURE TO THIRD PARTIES

In certain cases, it might become necessary to share personal information with law enforcement, legal or government authorities. These cases may arise from litigation, from public or government requests, or from national security reasons. In such cases, Cyfuture will be obliged to disclose your personal information to only the relevant authorities, and to inform you in such events.

In case of any mergers & acquisitions, sale of company assets or reorganization of the firm, Cyfuture may be required to transfer any and all data to third party or parties, including personal information.

### THIRD-PARTY SERVICES 

Cyfuture products and services might contain links that lead to third-party applications or resources. If you choose to visit or interact with those third parties and their affiliates, the data you provide to them is governed by their separate privacy policies, to which you should pay heed regarding the usage of your personal information by them. Cyfuture has no control or responsibility towards data collected, stored and manipulated by third parties.

### RETENTION OF PERSONAL DATA

We will retain your personal data for as long as needed to provide the access and use of the website unless a longer period of retention is required either by law, or is necessitated for a legitimate business purpose.

### INFORMATION SPECIFICALLY RELEVANT FOR EU USERS (GDPR)

Cyfuture is ardently pursuant of GDPR directives for data subjects in the EU. If you are a user of Cyfuture services in the European Union, you have the following rights with respect to Cyfuture’s handling of your personal information:

  * You can request an explanation of personal data processing, handling and usage by us;
  * You also have the right to receive a copy of the information that we collect about you whether the information is collected on the basis of consent or because the said information was required by us in order to provide the requested services.
  * You possess the right to withdraw your consent for personal data processing, at any time to prevent future processing;
  * You have the right to request correction of your personal data that has been stored with us in case you believe the same is not accurate;
  * You may request deletion of your personal data, provided this request does not contravene any laws or legal procedures;
  * You have the right to object to Cyfuture’s processing of their personal information; 
  * You can contact the relevant data protection authority for issues regarding your personal data.

**DATA TRANSFER :** In order for us to provide the services to you, your personal information will be transferred to, and stored at/processed in our servers in accordance with extant laws. Your personal data is also processed by staff operating in global locations. We will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your personal data is treated securely and in accordance with this policy.

### QUERIES REGARDING PRIVACY 

Cyfuture is always open to answering queries, providing clarifications and addressing concerns regarding your privacy. If you have any questions regarding this Privacy Policy, please contact us via e-mail at: [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#f282809b8493918bb2918b948786878097dc919d9f)

### PRIVACY POLICY UPDATES

We may update this privacy policy from time to time. We encourage you to periodically review this privacy to understand how Cyfuture is protecting your information. If any change is unacceptable to you, you have the right to cease using this website. If you do not do so, you will be deemed to have accepted our then current Privacy Policy.
